Guide to the Progressive Cities and Neighborhood Planning 1969-2005 Collection, 1969-2005
Progressive Cities and Neighborhood Planning 1969-2005 Collection, 1969-2005
- Series X: Interviews
  - Luria, Russell, 1981 (Box 20)
  - Sanders, Krumholz, 1980, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Zane, Deluros, Shearer, 1983 (Box 20)
    Santa Monica
  - Ancho, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Rice, Susan (Box 20)
  - Rhoden, Cheryl (Box 20)
  - Reed, Christine, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Cohn, Osbourne, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Myers, Goldway, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Austin, Jones (Box 20)
  - Hotchkiss, Frank, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Goldway, March 22, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Goldfarb, Shearer, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Edwards, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Harding, Alshuler, Rothstein, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Sullivan, December 10, 2004 (Box 20)
  - Klofas, 2004 (Box 20)
  - Johnson, December 21, 2004 (Box 20)
  - Clayton (Box 21)
    Boston
  - President of Charlestown Preservation Society, August 7, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Bledsoe, May 19, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Ansara, May 12, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Achtenberg, May 24, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Achtenberg, 1990 (Box 21)
  - Abrahamson, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Desanner, Jim, May 25, 2006 (Box 21)
    Binghamton
  - Clark, Mary, April 12, 2006 (Box 21)
  - Abdelazim, Tarik, March 28, 2006 (Box 21)
  - Hancock, Ilona, March 19, 1987 (Box 21)
    Berkley
  - Kirshner lecture, October 2, 1981 (Box 21)
  - Kirshner, 1981 (Box 21)
  - Bach, Boggan, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Bach, Eve, April 16, 1989 (Box 21)
  - Whisnant, Whitehead, May 11, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Lucas, C., April 22, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Lee, Suzanne, April 22, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Kennedy, M., 1990 (Box 21)
  - Gondek, Mikhael, September 19, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Gleason, Harold, August 6, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Fine, Janice, May 15, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Ferullo, Lucy, April 28, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Dreier, Fern, 1991 (Box 21)
  - Fauntleroy, Deborah (Box 21)
  - Dyer, Mark, May 5, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Fahrer, April 17, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Dreier, 1989-1991 (Box 21)
  - Draisen, Mark, October 5, 1999 (Box 21)
  - DeModis, Paul (Box 21)
  - McAfee, Kathy (Box 21)
  - McCormeck, K. (Box 21)
  - McQuigan, Pat (Box 21)
  - Medoff, May 14, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Morley, Daniel, July 31, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Mustafa, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Newport, Gus, April 15, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Nye, Nancy, February 19, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Salerno, April 27, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Siegal, Saunders, August 17, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Scondras, May 19, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Schwartz, Marilyn, February 19, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Simmons (Box 21)
  - Snyder, Nancy, May 5, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Snyder, Tom, May 6, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Staples, Lee, March 25, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Thall, Matt (Box 21)
  - Turner, April 30, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Wade, J., May 15, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Walker, Pat, May 14, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Wao, Webb (Box 21)
  - Dunn, Martin, 1997 (Box 21)
    Brooklyn
  - Schiffman, November 29, 2005 (Box 21)
- Series XI: Interview Transcripts
  - Alschuler, Carbone, Cochrane, Coleman, Dollard, Gold, Lumsden, Merrow, Mimnaugh, Ritter, Wilson, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Mier, Carlson, Longworth, Shier, Lemonides, Clark, Wysocki, Masotti, Mosena, Crutchfield, Sawislak, Weiner, Elam, Crowe, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Olivero, Cizon, Werth, Mike, Santiago, Melriphy, Lawrence, Lavalle, Lamont, Thurow, Kane, Chico, Rivere, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Brehm, Clark, Giloth, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Mier, Cassell, Ducharme, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Bennett, Clark, Gills, Gonzales, Reardon, Ramsey, Hellwig, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kennedy, Marie, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Achtenberg, Ansara, Jones, Schiewe, Younger, Marzilli, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bledsoe, Coyle (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Dyen, Ferullo, Fahrer, Fine, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Fishbein, Gondek, Kane, Kennedy, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Lee, McAfee, Medoff, Newport, Nye, Solerno, 1986-1992 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Scondras, Snyder, Staples, Turner, Wade, Walker, West, 1986-2004 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Sartelle, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Anger, Shearer, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Kirshner, Bach, Boggan, Hancock, Newport, 1981-1989 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Berkeley
  - Green, Mayo, Sequoia, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Benington, 1980s (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Michie, Laburn, Wainwright, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Ward, Darwin, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Darwin, Blunkett, Jackson, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Lesser, Roger, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Series XII: Neighborhood Planning
  Files currently retained by donor.
- Series XIII: Other